Eloise Hubbard Linscott collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - SR311, 1943 or 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr311b
      - Amsterdam
  - SR312, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Maynard Reynolds, in Pittsburg, New Hampshire. Original disc recordings with ID numbers SR311-SR313 (inclusive) were received from the collector housed together in a Recordisc Corporation paper wrapper. Collector’s original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr312a
      - Gay Gold Chain
      - Drowsy Sleeper [Who's That At My Bedroom Window]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr312b
      - Untitled
      - Burial At Sea
      - Peter Anderson
  - SR313, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr313a
      - Jimmy Whalen [Lost Jimmy Whalen]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr313b
      - Mary Came Down the Mountainside
  - SR314, November 9, 1941 (for Farnham); November 12, 1941 (for Brown), 1 10-inch disc
    All performances by Herbert D. (Bert) Farnham (fiddle; in Swanville, Maine), except "Flora, the Lily of the West," performed by Asa Brown, in Carthage, Maine. The recordings of Farnham on Side A were made at the wrong speed (too fast).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr314a
      - Music for the dance Boston Fancy: Drunken Sailor
      - Flora, the Lily of the West
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr314b
      - Hull's Victory
      - Devil's Dream
      - Untitled
      - Old Zip Coon
      - Music for the dance Boston Fancy: Drunken Sailor
  - SR315, April 7, 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Gene Staples (fiddle), plus spoken introduction for “Beaux of Albany”, in Dixfield, Maine.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr315a
      - Beaux of Albany
      - My Love's A Lassie Yet [My Love Is But A Lassie Yet]
      - Devil's Dream
    - Side B: Music for the dance Lady of the Lake, afc1942002_sr315b
      - Enterprise and Boxer
      - Ricketts Hornpipe
      - Monkey's Wedding (Sailor's Hornpipe)
      - Come, Haste to the Wedding [Haste to the Wedding]
  - SR316, November 14 or 24, 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Llewelyn S. Powers (fiddle, Side A, tune 1); Mrs. Belle Webber (fiddle) of Hillsborough, New Hampshire (Side A, tune 2). An unidentified person plays piano on "Petronella." Side B: Mrs. Belle Webber (fiddle, for the first two tunes). The testing segment may have been recorded from a radio broadcast. Collector's original ID: XXVIII.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr316a
      - Mr. Powers's own composition
      - Petronella [Patronella; Green Mountain Petronella]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr316b
      - Petronella [Patronella; Green Mountain Petronella]
      - Come Up the Back Stairs
      - Testing
  - SR317, January 9, 1942, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Llewellyn S. Powers (fiddle). An unidentified person accompanied him on piano. Collector’s original ID: VII.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr317a
      - Devil's Dream
      - Hornpipe
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr317b
      - Hull's Victory
      - Speed the Plow [Speed the Plough]
  - SR318, undated, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Llewellyn S. Powers (fiddle). An unidentified person accompanied him on piano. Collector’s original ID: XI.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr318a
      - Lady Walpole's Reel
      - Sailor's Hornpipe
    - Side B: Music for the dance Virginia Reel, afc1942002_sr318b
      - Irish Washerwoman
      - White Cockade
      - Yankee Doodle
      - Mr. Powers's own composition (fragment)
  - SR319, circa 1940-1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Dennis McClure, of Willimantic, Connecticut, is the caller for “Captain Jinks.” The testing segment may have been recorded from a radio broadcast. Side B: Performed by Llewellyn S. Powers (fiddle).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr319a
      - Testing
      - Golden Slippers/
      - Captain Jinks
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr319b
      - Hull's Victory
      - American Hornpipes
      - Arkansas Traveler
  - SR320, December 29, 1945, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr320a
      - Irish Washerwoman
      - The Girl I Left Behind Me
      - Pop Goes the Weasel
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr320b
      - I Can't Untie the Knot (with variations)
      - Uncle Sam's Hornpipe
  - SR321, November 12, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: performed Alvin Brown, in Carthage, Maine. Side B: performed by Gene Staples, in Dixfield, Maine.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr321a
      - Lumberman's Alphabet
      - Klondike Jail
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr321b
      - Dan Weaver (two fragments)
      - When the Roll Is Called Up Yonder
  - SR322, September 8, 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Edward Reed. Collector’s original ID: III
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr322a
      - Billy Boy
      - Tittery Nan
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr322b
      - Whisky Johnny
      - Tommy's Gone to Hilo
      - Captain Kidd
      - Canaday I-O
  - SR323, September 28, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    New Hampshire Guides Band; Harvey (Doc) Converse, leader. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr323a
      - Soldier's Joy
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr323b
      - Waltzes
  - SR324, October 29, 1943, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Carrie B. Grover, in Gorham, Maine. Collector's original ID: XIV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr324a
      - Fair Fanny Moore (fragment)
      - Banks of the Nile
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr324b
      - Banks of the Nile (continued)
  - SR325, September 23, 1947, 1 6-inch disc
    Performers/speakers: Sammy Tomah and Sebat Tomah, in Peter Dana Point, Maine. Collector’s original ID: I. Side A: both sections of this side are spoken, probably in Passamaquoddy; the second seems to be a discussion between the two men. Side B: both men speak, probably in Passamaquoddy.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr325a
      - Untitled
      - Untitled
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr325b
      - Chief Sammy introduces himself and councillor Sebat then Sebat talks too re [sic]
  - SR326, January 14 and 16, 1942, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Mrs. Ada Ford (Side A, song 1). Other female singers on the disc are not yet identified.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr326a
      - Micmac Indian Song
      - Gay Gallant Maid
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr326b
      - The Dying Nun
  - SR327, October 29, 1943, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Carrie B. Grover, in Gorham, Maine. Collector’s original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr327a
      - Foggy Dew
      - Greenwood Siding (fragment)
      - The Jolly Roving Tar
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr327b
      - Leather Britches
      - Hold Your Tongue Dear Sally
      - Me Coat Is Tore
  - SR328, October 29, 1943, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Carrie B. Grover, in Gorham, Maine. Collector’s original ID: V.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr328a
      - Crockery Ware
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr328b
      - Hurley Burley
      - Oaks of James Deering [Oaks of James Dearing]
      - Susan, the Pride of Kildare
      - Lovely Flora or Erin Go Bragh
  - SR329, January 1, 1943, 1 6-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr329a
      - Ben Lomand
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr329b
      - Over the Waves
  - SR330, circa 1943-1944, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Will E. Ayer, of Fitchburg, Massachusetts. No audible recording on either disc side.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr330a
      - Battle of Lake Champlain
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr330b
      - Irish Washerwoman
      - Yankee Volunteer
  - SR331, July 31, 1946, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Llewelyn S. Powers (fiddle). Collector’s original ID: VIII. Linscott acknowledge in the documentation that Side B was not a good recording.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr331a
      - Lady in the Pump Room [Maid in the Pump Room]
      - Heel and Toe Polka
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr331b
      - Lady in the Pump Room, January 9, 1942, 1 6-inch disc
        Performed by Llewelyn S. Powers (fiddle).
  - SR332
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr332a
      - Devil's Dream
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr332b
      - Fisher's Hornpipe
  - SR333, November 11, 1944, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Albert Quigley (fiddle), of Nelson, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: V.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr333a
      - Top of Cork Road
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr333b
      - Merry Dance
  - SR334, November 11, 1944, 1 6-inch disc
    Performed by Albert Quigley (fiddle), of Nelson, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr334a
      - President Hornpipe
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr334b
      - Durang's Hornpipe
  - SR335, April 16, 1940, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by the Texas Ramblers (Dave White, leader, and Doreen Ainsworth, caller), Saint Johnsbury, Vermont. Collector’s original ID: XII.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr335a
      - Duck for the Oyster Quadrille (Part 1) (with calls)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr335b
      - Honest John (with calls)
  - SR336, undated, 1 8-inch disc
    Side A: songs 1 and 2 performed by KW (female singer, with guitar accompaniment), song 3 performed by Eloise Hubbard Linscott. Side B: “Old Merchant” performed by KW; all other songs performed by Edson H. Cole (fiddle and calls), in Freedom, New Hampshire. Piano accompaniment by an unidentified person. Collector’s original ID: XV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr336a
      - Three Crows
      - Ship A-Sailing
      - Springfield Mountain
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr336b
      - Soldier’s Joy
      - Music for the dance Lady of the Lake
        - Haste to the Wedding [1]
        - Old Merchant
      - Music for the dance Lady of the Lake
        - Haste to the Wedding [2]
        - Durang’s Hornpipe
  - SR337, January 9, 1942, 1 8-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr337a
      - Speed the Plough [Speed the Plow]
      - Old Zip Coon
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr337b
      - Pop Goes the Weasel
      - Douglas' Favorite
  - SR338, April 22, 1943 (Side A); April 21, 1943 (Side B), 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by Lillian M. Cheney.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr338a
      - Old Frog in the Spring
      - Untitled
      - Old Ironsides
      - Come Sister Come
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr338b
      - Erin Go Bragh
      - Gypsy Daisy [Gypsy Davey]
      - Jim Fiske
  - SR339, November 14, 1940, 1 8-inch disc
    Side A: Mrs. Frank Roberts, of Manchester, New Hampshire, for “Finnegan’s Wake.” Mrs. Belle Webber (fiddle), of Hillsborough, New Hampshire, for “Ladies Triumph.” Webber also plays fiddle for all tunes on Side B.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr339a
      - Finnegan's Wake
      - Ladies Triumph
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr339b
      - Oyster River
      - Sweet Betsy from the Pike
  - SR340, April 17, 1940, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by Sam Young, Jr., in Laconia, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: XVII.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr340a
      - Maid of the Mountain Brow
      - Lass of the Mohea (second verse) [Lass of Mohea; Little Mohea]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr340b
      - High, Low, Jack, and the Game
  - SR341, December 8, 1941 (Side A); January 5, 1942 (Side B), 1 8-inch disc
    Side A: the speaker is Franklin D. (Franklin Delano) Roosevelt. This side was recorded from a radio broadcast. Side B: John Hubbard Linscott plays the clarinet; while uncredited, Eloise Hubbard Linscott is probably the pianist.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr341a
      - Roosevelt Asks for Declaration of War versus Japan (Part 3)
      - Star Spangled Banner (fragment)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr341b
      - Untitled clarinet tune
      - Untitled clarinet and piano duet
  - SR342, December 8, 1941, 1 8-inch disc
    The speaker is Franklin D. (Franklin Delano) Roosevelt. Both sides were recorded from a radio broadcast. Collector's original IDs: I (Side A); II (Side B)
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr342a
      - Roosevelt Asks for Declaration of War versus Japan (Part 1)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr342b
      - Roosevelt Asks for Declaration of War versus Japan (Part 2)
  - SR343, circa early November 1940, 1 8-inch disc
    The speaker is Wendell Lewis Wilkie. An unidentified woman speaks at the end of Side B. Both sides were recorded from a radio broadcast. The content of the recordings is almost inaudible.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr343a
      - Eve of Election to President
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr343b
      - Eve of Election to President
  - SR344, March 22, 1941, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by Llewellyn S. Powers (fiddle). An unidentified pianist accompanies Powers.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr344a
      - Wolfeboro Hornpipe
      - Lily of the Valley
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr344b
      - The Little Old Log Cabin in the Lane
  - SR345, February 1942, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by David M. (Dave) Swett. Collector’s original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr345a
      - The Bummer's Reel
      - Music for the dance Lady of the Lake: Fisher's Hornpipe
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr345b
      - Old Zip Coon
      - Portland Fancy
  - SR346, February 1942, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by David M. (Dave) Swett (fiddle), of Framingham, Massachusetts. Collector's original ID: VII (Side A); VIII (Side B).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr346a
      - Music for the dance Boston Fancy: Durang's Hornpipe
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr346b
      - Miss McLeod's Reel
      - Douglas' Favorite
  - SR347, February 1942, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by David M. (Dave) Swett (fiddle), of Framingham, Massachusetts. Collector’s original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr347a
      - Speed the Plough
      - Devil's Dream
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr347b
      - Chorus Jig
  - SR348, February 1942, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by David M. (Dave) Swett (fiddle), of Framingham, Massachusetts. Collector's original ID: I (Side A); II (Side B).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr348a
      - Liverpool Hornpipe
      - Old Zip Coon
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr348b
      - Tuning
      - Soldier's Joy
  - SR349, April 17, 1940, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by Sam Young, Jr., in Laconia, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: XVI.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr349a
      - Jack Haggerty (partial)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr349b
      - The Jam on Gerry's Rocks (partial)
  - SR350, undated, 1 8-inch disc
    Side A: performed by Ethel Fuller. Side B: unidentified orchestra (for "Old Macdonald Had a Farm"). Eloise Hubbard Linscott (as "Ele") is credited with all other songs on the disc side. Side A and Linscott's portion of Side B are almost inaudible. Linscott notes (on the disc sleeve) that the disc cutting machine is "acting cranky" during the recording. Collector’s original ID: XIV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr350a
      - In Good Old Colony Times
      - Fair Rosamund [Fair Rosamond]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr350b
      - Old MacDonald Had a Farm
      - Arkansas Traveler
      - Untitled
      - Away Down East
      - Brookfield Murder
  - SR351, circa April or August 1940 (Side A); circa 1943-1953 (Side B), 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by Dennis McClure (calls and banjo), of Willimantic, Connecticut.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr351a
      - Turkey in the Straw [with calls and banjo solo]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr351b
      - How Dry I Am
      - Missouri Waltz
  - SR352, undated, 1 8-inch disc
    Recorded from radio broadcast(s) on WORL.
    - Side A: Advertisements, afc1942002_sr352a
      - Saturday Evening Post
      - Paradise Wine
      - Pepsi Cola/
      - Lifebuoy
    - Side B: Advertisements, afc1942002_sr352b
      - I Am A Happy Medium (Ex Lax)
      - G. Washington
      - Dawson's Ale
      - Virginia Dare
  - SR353, undated, 1 8-inch disc
    Side B is blank.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr353a
      - Old Zip Coon
  - SR354, May 14, 1949 (Side A); circa 1943-1953 (Side B), 1 8-inch disc
    Side A: Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus; William J. (Jack) Sherrard, soloist.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr354a
      - Rio Grande [Ryo Grande]
    - Side B: Sound Effects, afc1942002_sr354b
      - Capstan Blocks
      - Wind
      - Sea
  - SR355, August 18, 1948, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by the Shaker Singers, of Enfield, New Hampshire. According to Linscott's notes, three stanzas are missing from the song "The Humble Heart." Collector’s original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr355a
      - I Have A Little Drum (with sound effects/gestures)
      - Precept and Line
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr355b
      - The Humble Heart
  - SR356, circa 1943-1953, 1 8-inch disc
    Side A may have been recorded from a radio broadcast. Side B: New Hampshire Guides Band. This side may be a copy of another disc.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr356a
      - Waltzes
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr356b
      - Soldier's Joy
  - SR357, March 18, 1950, 1 8-inch disc
    Side A: the duet is performed by Helen Remick and Pauline (Polly) Remick. Both solos (Sides A and B) performed by Pauline (Polly) Remick. Both singers are from Concord, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr357a
      - Little Dicky (duet) [Little Dicky Dilver]
      - Little Dicky (solo) [Little Dicky Dilver]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr357b
      - Little Dicky [solo; fragment] [Little Dicky Dilver]
  - SR358, circa 1941-1942, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by Dennis McClure (the caller), Willimantic, Connecticut. He may also be the banjo player (both disc sides).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr358a
      - Soldier's Joy (with calls)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr358b
      - Hartley's Reel (breakdown)
      - Untitled
  - SR359, January 17, 1947, 1 8-inch disc
    Performed by Edson H. Cole (fiddle), in Freedom, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr359a
      - Soldier's Joy
      - The Tempest
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr359b
  - SR360, August 29, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr360a
      - Nobody's Child/Burial at Sea
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr360b
      - Lord Bateman
  - SR361, circa 1946-1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Maynard Reynolds, Pittsburg, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr361a
      - Lake of Ponchatrain
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr361b
      - The Scolding Wife
      - Four Cousins
      - Old Dan Day
  - SR362, February 7, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by L.C. (Pop) Brock (banjo and vocals). Side B is blank.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr362a
      - Oh Susanna
      - Duck Foot Sue
  - SR363, March 31, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded at a 4-H dance, in Lebanon, New Hampshire. David Mann is the caller.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr363a
      - David Mann gives instructions to the dancers
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr363b
      - David Mann gives instructions to the dancers (continued)
      - Four Leaf Clover [I'm Looking Over a Four Leaf Clover]
  - SR364, March 31, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: an unidentified person plays "Lili Marlene" on the piano. All other tracks recorded at a 4-H dance, in Lebanon, New Hampshire. David Mann is the caller.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr364a
      - Lili Marlene
      - David Mann gives instructions to the dancers
      - Lili Marlene
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr364b
      - David Mann gives instructions to the dancers (continued)
      - Rose of San Antone
  - SR365, April 2, 1951 (Side A); March 31, 1950 (Side B), 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: performed by Val Hardy (fiddle), in Enfield, New Hampshire. Side B: Recorded at a 4-H dance, in Lebanon, New Hampshire. David Mann is the caller. An unidentified person is featured on the fiddle. Collector’s original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr365a
      - Devil's Dream
      - My Love Is But A Lassie [My Love Is But A Lassie Yet]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr365b
      - Four Leaf Clover (with calls) [I'm Looking Over a Four Leaf Clover]
  - SR366, April 2, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Val Hardy (fiddle), in Enfield, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr366a
      - Portland Fancy
      - Patronella [Petronella]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr366b
      - Soldier's Joy
  - SR367, April 2, 1951, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Val Hardy (fiddle), in Enfield, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr367a
      - Cincinnati Hornpipe
      - Polka
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr367b
      - Portland Fancy
  - SR368, August 8, 1948, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Milton Appleby (fiddle) and Mrs. Milton Appleby (piano), in Gonic, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: IV.
    - Side A: Music for the dance Heel and Toe Polka, afc1942002_sr368a
      - I Have a Bonnet Trimmed in Blue
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr368b
      - Inverness Gathering
      - Trip to the Isle [Trip to the Isles]
  - SR369, circa 1941-1942, 1 10-inch disc
    "Untitled [1]" is too distorted to identify. "Untitled [2]," "Blow, Bloys, Blow," and "Springfield Mountain" may be performed by Eloise Hubbard Linscott, accompanying herself on piano. "Hull's Victory" performed by Edson H. Cole (fiddle and calls), Freedom, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr369a
      - Untitled [1]
      - Untitled [2]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr369b
      - Hull's Victory
      - Blow Boys Blow
      - Springfield Mountain
  - SR370, September 26, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Eugene (Gene) Andrews (fiddle), in Norway, Maine. Side B: introduction includes an unidentified man asking Andrews a few questions. Collector’s original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr370a
      - The Girl I Left Behind Me
      - Pop Goes the Weasel
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr370b
      - Introduction
      - Haste to the Wedding [Come Haste to the Wedding]
      - Turkey in the Straw
  - SR371, September 26, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Eugene (Gene) Andrews (fiddle), in Norway, Maine. Collector's original ID: V on label; IV on disc sleeve.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr371a
      - Oldtime waltz
      - Old waltz
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr371b
      - Money Musk [Monymusk]
      - Pampas Plume
  - SR372, September 27, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Abraham (Abe) Washburn, in Kidderville, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr372a
      - Benjamin Dean
      - Wild River Tragedy [1]
      - Wild River Tragedy [2]
      - Four Cousins
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr372b
      - P.O.
      - P.O. (another verse)
      - Etta Lee
  - SR373, January 21, 1942 (Side A); November 9, 1941 (Side B), 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: "The Waltz" performed by Joanne [Audlin?] on piano. "Come Philander" and "Charlie Is a Dandy" performed by Mrs. Crosby, of Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts. Side B: Performers include Betty Gaye Farnham, of Swanville, Maine, and Eloise Hubbard Linscott. "Old Man Worth [1]" is nearly inaudible. Both versions of "Old Man Worth" seem to have been recorded at the wrong speed.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr373a
      - The Waltz
      - Come Philander [fragments]
      - Charlie Is A Dandy [fragment]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr373b
      - Old Man Worth[1]
      - Old Man Worth[2]
      - Discussion between Linscott and Betty Gaye Farnham
      - Untitled piano piece (fragment)
  - SR374, July 23, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr374a
      - Woodstock Wreck
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr374b
      - Woodstock Wreck (Chapter II)
      - When A Young Feller's Gone on a Girl [Kissing Song]
  - SR375, September 25, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Charles W. (Charlie) Porter, Lancaster, New Hampshire. Collector’s original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr375a
      - Ally with the Long Nose
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr375b
      - Jud Potter
  - SR376, July 12, 1955, 1 10-inch disc
    Documentation indicates this is a recording of Brother Ricardo Belden, of Lenox, Massachusetts. However, the content is almost inaudible, with sporadic moments of piano playing. At the end of the side, a male voice can be heard to say "What the hell is going on here anyway?" Side B is blank.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr376a
      - Untitled
  - SR377, November 21, 1950, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Charles Jenney.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr377a
      - Tib the Grey Mare (fragment) [Tibb the Grey Mare]